<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CI/CD | Chao Péter Yang</title>
    <link>https://site-cpyang.github.io/tag/ci/cd/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://site-cpyang.github.io/tag/ci/cd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>CI/CD</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://site-cpyang.github.io/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>CI/CD</title>
      <link>https://site-cpyang.github.io/tag/ci/cd/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>SanAssist: LLM-Powered Healthcare Data Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://site-cpyang.github.io/project/sanassist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://site-cpyang.github.io/project/sanassist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SanAssist is an innovative web application that empowers healthcare professionals with seamless data analysis and natural language querying. The platform combines interactive dashboards built with the Squirrels library and a fine-tuned GPT-2 model (via LoRA) to deliver context-aware insights from patient datasets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The system includes a complete ETL pipeline (Databricks + Pandas) for data ingestion, transformation, and storage, connected to a lightweight Python microservice. Healthcare professionals can upload datasets, explore interactive charts and tables, and query the integrated chatbot for insights like &lt;em&gt;“Which patients are at the highest risk for sepsis?”&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SanAssist is fully containerized with Docker, deployed on AWS Elastic Container Registry (ECR) and App Runner, and automated via GitHub Actions CI/CD pipelines. Load tests with 10,000 concurrent users confirmed scalability, with peak throughput of 602 RPS. The fine-tuned model achieved a perplexity score of &lt;strong&gt;3.32&lt;/strong&gt;, outperforming general-purpose medical LLMs such as Med-PaLM in domain-specific accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a robust data pipeline, secure deployment, and intuitive interface, SanAssist demonstrates how LLMs can transform healthcare analytics, bridging the gap between raw data and actionable clinical insights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
